{
    "id": "108_Entertainment_640",
    "claim": "Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling, is also known for taking extreme care of his character. It has stopped events bearing the name Santo and also projects for profit. His demands are so many, that in recent years he has fought only sporadically, for most of his time he uses it by going through courts. These are some of the strangest demands made by the Son of the Holy, except that of the memes, which already had its own cover. EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS. SANTOS LAGUNAThe Son of the Holy One sued the soccer team Santos Laguna in  for the misuse of the name. Although he lost his first instance because the team is named after him because 'santos 'is the popular gentile of the town of Santa Cruz, Tlaxcala (where the team was called Santos de la Trinidad), the sentence has been appealed, with the argument that said people plagiarized the name of the same fighter. EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS. INTERNATIONAL OLIMPIC COMITEThe fighter launched this demand at the beginning of this century seeking that the Olympic Games should stop awarding the silver medal. 'There are many metals that can be chosen, such as tin and alpaca ', can be read in demand. The wrestler lost the litigation in  due to his own argument, for the alpaca is not a metal, but an alloy. EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS. THE RIVER PLATEThe masked man made a tour of Argentina, and first planned to sue the country, but learned that it is no longer called Viceroyalty of Rio de la Plata. For this reason, and in order to take advantage of the trip, he sued the football team River Plate, which is named after Rio de la Plata, he also lost this litigation within a few months, as the judge ruled that 'plate 'means 'plate ', and not 'silver '. Argentines were ridiculed for not being able to translate, but they saved themselves from that demand that demanded  millions of dollars. EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS. RODOLFO GUZMÁN HUERTAOne of the most controversial demands was made by the fighter against Rodolfo Guzmán for having used the character of Santo for decades without his consent. The demand required the payment of  millions of dollars plus operating expenses. After a week, the Son of the Holy One himself withdrew the lawsuit when he realized a small detail, to which he exclaimed:'Oh, shit! If that's my dad!\". I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.eldizque.com",
    "date": "25/10/2017",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling , is also known for taking extreme care of character.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is Son of the Holy One?",
                    "answer": "one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of Mexican wrestling?",
                    "score": 0.7426,
                    "answers": "the history of Mexican wrestling|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Son of the Holy One known for taking extreme care of character?",
                    "score": 0.705,
                    "answers": "for taking extreme care of character|prep\textreme care of character|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "taking has stopped events bearing the name Santo and also projects for profit.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.eldizque.com report on 25/10/2017?",
                    "answer": "taking has stopped events bearing the name Santo"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many events has taking stopped events?",
                    "score": 0.746,
                    "answers": "that taking has stopped events bearing the name Santo and also projects for profit|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the profit of taking events bearing Santo and also projects for profit?",
                    "score": 0.656,
                    "answers": "profit|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the event that has stopped events bearing the name Santo?",
                    "score": 0.6176,
                    "answers": "the|det\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Santo?",
                    "score": 0.5788,
                    "answers": "25/10/2017|pobj\tbearing the name Santo|acl\tthe name Santo|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between taking and the Santo event?",
                    "score": 0.57,
                    "answers": "also projects for profit|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "demands are so many, that in recent years Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling has fought only sporadically, for most of time Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling uses it by going through courts.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldizque.com report that demands are so many that in recent years Son of the Holy One has fought only sporadically?",
                    "answer": "25/10/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How does the Son of the Holy One use taquileros?",
                    "score": 0.8162,
                    "answers": "through courts|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "These are some of the strangest demands made by Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling , except that of the memes, which already had its own cover .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is Son of the Holy One?",
                    "answer": "one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are Son of the Holy One's demands on taquileros in history of Mexican wrestling?",
                    "score": 0.7695,
                    "answers": "its own cover|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the demands of Son of Holy One?",
                    "score": 0.7242,
                    "answers": "taquileros|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many memes have had their own cover?",
                    "score": 0.6941,
                    "answers": "except that of the memes , which already had its own cover|prep\tthe memes , which already had its own cover|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.eldizque.com report that EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THEHOLY VS. THE HOLY?",
                    "answer": "25/10/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the relationship between Oswald and Rodrigo Duterte?",
                    "score": 0.6243,
                    "answers": "on 25/10/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the significance ofNUMBER�SON OF THE HOLY VISION?",
                    "score": 0.5848,
                    "answers": "that EXPEDIENT # NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of \"NUMBER�SON OF THE HOLY VISION\"?",
                    "score": 0.5762,
                    "answers": "NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between greed and science?",
                    "score": 0.5528,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 25/10/2017 that EXPEDIENT # NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the website \"eldizque.com\"?",
                    "score": 0.5338,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "SANTOS LAGUNAThe Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling sued SANTOS LAGUNAThe in  for the misuse of the name.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldizque.com report that SANTOS LAGUNAThe sued SANTOS LAGUNAThe?",
                    "answer": "25/10/2017"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is SANTOS LAGUNAThe Son of the Holy One?",
                    "answer": "one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who sued SANTOS LAGUNA?",
                    "score": 0.7937,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 25/10/2017 that SANTOS LAGUNAThe Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling sued SANTOS LAGUNAThe in|ROOT\tthat SANTOS LAGUNAThe Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling sued SANTOS LAGUNAThe in|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of SANTOS LAGUNA?",
                    "score": 0.6285,
                    "answers": "  for the misuse of the name|dep\tfor the misuse of the name|prep\tthe misuse of the name|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SANTOS LAGUNA?",
                    "score": 0.6196,
                    "answers": "on 25/10/2017|prep\t25/10/2017|pobj\tSANTOS|compound\tmost|advmod\ttaquileros|conj\tin the history of Mexican wrestling|prep\tthe history of Mexican wrestling|pobj\tof Mexican wrestling|prep\tMexican wrestling|pobj\tSANTOS|compound\tof the name|prep\tthe name|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is SANTOS LAGUNA?",
                    "score": 0.6163,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj\tthat|mark\tSANTOS LAGUNAThe Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|nsubj\tSon of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|appos\tof the Holy One|prep\tthe|det\tHoly|compound\t,|punct\tone of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|appos\tof the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|prep\tthe|det\tmost talented|amod\tthe most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|pobj\tand|cc\tthe|det\tin|prep\tthe|det\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Although Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling lost first instance because SANTOS LAGUNAThe is named after Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling because 'santos 'is the popular gentile of the town of Santa Cruz, Tlaxcala (where SANTOS LAGUNAThe was called Santos de la Trinidad), the sentence has been appealed, with the argument that said people plagiarized the name of Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the popular gentile of the town of Santa Cruz, Tlaxcala?",
                    "answer": "'santos"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many times has SANTOS LAGUNA been named after Son of the Holy One?",
                    "score": 0.7582,
                    "answers": "first instance|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is SANTOS LAGUNAThe named after?",
                    "score": 0.7234,
                    "answers": "Although Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling lost first instance because SANTOS LAGUNAThe is named after Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling because ' santos ' is the popular gentile of the town of Santa Cruz , Tlaxcala ( where SANTOS LAGUNAThe was called Santos de la Trinidad )|advcl\tthat Although Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling lost first instance because SANTOS LAGUNAThe is named after Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling because ' santos ' is the popular gentile of the town of Santa Cruz , Tlaxcala ( where SANTOS LAGUNAThe was called Santos de la Trinidad ) , the sentence has been appealed , with the argument that said people plagiarized the name of Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is SANTOS LAGUNA?",
                    "score": 0.6956,
                    "answers": "on 25/10/2017|prep\tone of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|appos\tof the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|prep\tmost talented|amod\tthe most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|pobj\tin the history of Mexican wrestling|prep\tafter Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|prep\tone of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|appos\tof the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|prep\tmost talented|amod\tthe most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|pobj\tin the history of Mexican wrestling|prep\tof Santa Cruz , Tlaxcala|prep\tpeople|nsubj\tone of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|appos\tof the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|prep\tmost talented|amod\tthe most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling|pobj\tin the history of Mexican wrestling|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SANTOS LAGUNA?",
                    "score": 0.6904,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj\tthe history of Mexican wrestling|pobj\tof Mexican wrestling|prep\tMexican wrestling|pobj\tbecause|mark\tSANTOS|compound\tis|auxpass\tthe history of Mexican wrestling|pobj\tof Mexican wrestling|prep\tMexican wrestling|pobj\tbecause|mark\t'|punct\t'|punct\tpopular|amod\tSanta Cruz , Tlaxcala|pobj\twhere|advmod\tSANTOS|compound\twhere SANTOS LAGUNAThe was called Santos de la Trinidad|relcl\tla|compound\t)|punct\tthe sentence|nsubjpass\thas|aux\tthe history of Mexican wrestling|pobj\tof Mexican wrestling|prep\tMexican wrestling|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the town of Santa Cruz, Tlaxcala?",
                    "score": 0.6826,
                    "answers": "because SANTOS LAGUNAThe is named after Son of the Holy One , one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling because ' santos ' is the popular gentile of the town of Santa Cruz , Tlaxcala ( where SANTOS LAGUNAThe was called Santos de la Trinidad )|advcl\tbecause ' santos ' is the popular gentile of the town of Santa Cruz , Tlaxcala ( where SANTOS LAGUNAThe was called Santos de la Trinidad|advcl\tthe popular gentile of the town of Santa Cruz , Tlaxcala ( where SANTOS LAGUNAThe was called Santos de la Trinidad|attr\tof the town of Santa Cruz , Tlaxcala ( where SANTOS LAGUNAThe was called Santos de la Trinidad|prep\tthe town of Santa Cruz , Tlaxcala ( where SANTOS LAGUNAThe was called Santos de la Trinidad|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.eldizque.com report that EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THEHOLY VS. THE HOLY?",
                    "answer": "25/10/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the relationship between Oswald and Rodrigo Duterte?",
                    "score": 0.6243,
                    "answers": "on 25/10/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the significance ofNUMBER�SON OF THE HOLY VISION?",
                    "score": 0.5848,
                    "answers": "that EXPEDIENT # NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of \"NUMBER�SON OF THE HOLY VISION\"?",
                    "score": 0.5762,
                    "answers": "NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between greed and science?",
                    "score": 0.5528,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 25/10/2017 that EXPEDIENT # NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the website \"eldizque.com\"?",
                    "score": 0.5338,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "INTERNATIONAL OLIMPIC Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling launched this demand at the beginning of this century seeking that the Olympic Games should stop awarding the silver medal.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the INTERNATIONAL OLIMPIC Son of the Holy One?",
                    "answer": "one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many taquileros have been awarded in history of Mexican wrestling?",
                    "score": 0.7104,
                    "answers": "taquileros|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of how many medals has INTERNATIONAL OLIMPIC been awarded?",
                    "score": 0.6748,
                    "answers": "this century|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the demand for the Olympic Games?",
                    "score": 0.662,
                    "answers": "at the beginning of this century|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is INTERNATIONAL OLIMPIC Son of the Holy One?",
                    "score": 0.6008,
                    "answers": "most talented|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'There are many metals that can be chosen, such as tin and alpaca ', can be read in demand.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What are two metals that can be chosen?",
                    "answer": "tin and alpaca"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What metals can be read in demand?",
                    "score": 0.8784,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj\tsuch as tin and alpaca|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many metals can be chosen?",
                    "score": 0.8424,
                    "answers": "many metals that can be chosen , such as tin and alpaca|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Son of the Holy One, one of the most talented wrestlers and taquileros in the history of Mexican wrestling lost the litigation in  due to own argument, for the alpaca is not a metal, but an alloy.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldizque.com report that Son of the Holy One lost the litigation?",
                    "answer": "25/10/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did the Son of the Holy One lose the litigation in the history of Mexican wrestling?",
                    "score": 0.7611,
                    "answers": "the litigation|dobj\town argument , for the alpaca is not a metal , but an alloy|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the metal composition of alpaca?",
                    "score": 0.6737,
                    "answers": "most|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the properties of alpaca?",
                    "score": 0.6712,
                    "answers": "not a metal , but an alloy|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the origin of the alpaca?",
                    "score": 0.6242,
                    "answers": "in the history of Mexican wrestling|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is alpaca?",
                    "score": 0.6139,
                    "answers": "the alpaca|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.eldizque.com report that EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THEHOLY VS. THE HOLY?",
                    "answer": "25/10/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the relationship between Oswald and Rodrigo Duterte?",
                    "score": 0.6243,
                    "answers": "on 25/10/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the significance ofNUMBER�SON OF THE HOLY VISION?",
                    "score": 0.5848,
                    "answers": "that EXPEDIENT # NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of \"NUMBER�SON OF THE HOLY VISION\"?",
                    "score": 0.5762,
                    "answers": "NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between greed and science?",
                    "score": 0.5528,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 25/10/2017 that EXPEDIENT # NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the website \"eldizque.com\"?",
                    "score": 0.5338,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "THE RIVER PLATEThe masked man made a tour of Argentina, and first planned to sue the country, but learned that it is no longer called Viceroyalty of Rio de la Plata.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the masked man's name now?",
                    "answer": "Viceroyalty of Rio de la Plata"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the masked man say about the Viceroyalty of Rio de la Plata?",
                    "score": 0.7242,
                    "answers": "but|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the masked man that planned to sue the country of Argentina?",
                    "score": 0.676,
                    "answers": "THE RIVER PLATEThe masked man|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the river and the nation?",
                    "score": 0.5589,
                    "answers": "on 25/10/2017|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "For this reason, and in order to take advantage of the trip, he sued the football team River Plate, which is named after Rio de la Plata, he also lost this litigation within a few months, as the judge ruled that 'plate 'means 'plate ', and not 'silver '.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Marco Rubio do to take advantage of the trip?",
                    "score": 0.6756,
                    "answers": "to take advantage of the trip|acl\tof the trip|prep\tthe trip|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the judge rule about River Plate?",
                    "score": 0.6655,
                    "answers": "the judge|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the name of the river plate that was named after Rio de la Plata?",
                    "score": 0.6192,
                    "answers": "not|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of plate?",
                    "score": 0.6068,
                    "answers": "plate|nsubj\tthat ' plate ' means ' plate ' , and not ' silver '|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Argentines were ridiculed for not being able to translate, but they saved themselves from that demand that demanded  millions of dollars.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why were the Argentines ridiculed for not being able to translate?",
                    "score": 0.8837,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 25/10/2017 that Argentines were ridiculed for not being able to translate , but they saved themselves from that demand that demanded   millions of dollars|ROOT\tthat Argentines were ridiculed for not being able to translate , but they saved themselves from that demand that demanded|ccomp\tfor not being able to translate|prep\tnot being able to translate|pcomp\tto translate|xcomp\tfrom that demand that demanded|prep\tthat demand that demanded|pobj\tthat demanded|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How much money were the Argentines asked for?",
                    "score": 0.8341,
                    "answers": "on 25/10/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Argentines do to be able to translate?",
                    "score": 0.8298,
                    "answers": "able to translate|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How much money did the Argentines save themselves from being unable to translate?",
                    "score": 0.8232,
                    "answers": "were|auxpass"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.eldizque.com report that EXPEDIENT #NUMBER*/SON OF THEHOLY VS. THE HOLY?",
                    "answer": "25/10/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the relationship between Oswald and Rodrigo Duterte?",
                    "score": 0.6243,
                    "answers": "on 25/10/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the significance ofNUMBER�SON OF THE HOLY VISION?",
                    "score": 0.5848,
                    "answers": "that EXPEDIENT # NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of \"NUMBER�SON OF THE HOLY VISION\"?",
                    "score": 0.5762,
                    "answers": "NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between greed and science?",
                    "score": 0.5528,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 25/10/2017 that EXPEDIENT # NUMBER*/SON OF THE HOLY VS|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the website \"eldizque.com\"?",
                    "score": 0.5338,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "RODOLFO GUZMÁN HUERTAOne of the most controversial demands was made by the fighter against Rodolfo Guzmán for having used the character of Santo for decades without his consent.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the fighter that made one of the most controversial demands?",
                    "answer": "Rodolfo Guzmán"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What demands did Rodrigo Duterte make against Rodolfo Guzmán?",
                    "score": 0.8363,
                    "answers": "of the most controversial demands|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who did RODOLFO GUZMÁN HUERTA fight?",
                    "score": 0.8321,
                    "answers": "against Rodolfo Guzmán|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What demands were made against Rodolfo Guzmán?",
                    "score": 0.803,
                    "answers": "the most controversial demands|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who made the demands against Rodolfo Guzmán?",
                    "score": 0.7761,
                    "answers": "by the fighter|agent"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did RODOLFO Guzmán say about his demands?",
                    "score": 0.7695,
                    "answers": "RODOLFO|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The demand required the payment of  millions of dollars plus operating expenses.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many dollars were required to be paid in addition to operating expenses?",
                    "answer": "millions"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much did the demand for operating expenses cost?",
                    "score": 0.8371,
                    "answers": "  millions of dollars plus operating expenses|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How much money didldizque.com request for operating expenses?",
                    "score": 0.7866,
                    "answers": "on 25/10/2017|prep\t25/10/2017|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the demand require the payment of?",
                    "score": 0.7739,
                    "answers": "The|det\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the amount of operating expenses?",
                    "score": 0.7401,
                    "answers": "millions of dollars plus operating expenses|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the demand for the payment of  millions of dollars?",
                    "score": 0.7355,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 25/10/2017 that The demand required the payment of   millions of dollars plus operating expenses|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "After a week, the Son of the Holy One himself withdrew the lawsuit when he realized a small detail, to which he exclaimed:'Oh, shit! If that's my dad!\".",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldizque.com report that the Son of the Holy One withdrew the lawsuit?",
                    "answer": "25/10/2017"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Son of the Holy One say when he realized a small detail?",
                    "answer": "If that's my dad!\""
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did the Son of the Holy One withdraw the lawsuit?",
                    "score": 0.8044,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 25/10/2017 that After a week , the Son of the Holy One himself withdrew the lawsuit when he realized a small detail , to which he exclaimed:'Oh , shit ! If that 's my dad ! \"|ROOT\tAfter a week|prep\tthat After a week , the Son of the Holy One himself withdrew the lawsuit when he realized a small detail , to which he exclaimed:'Oh , shit ! If that 's my dad|ccomp\tthe lawsuit|dobj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}